>> SHE'S WELCOME VICTORIOUS ON
HER MEGAHIT NICKELODEON SHOW.
PLEASE WELCOME VICTORIA JUSTICE.
>> CUTE LITTLE OUTFIT.
>> THANK YOU.
>> THE LAST TIME YOU WERE HERE
YOU WERE HOW OLD?
>> I THINK I WAS 16.
I'M 18 NOW.
>> CONGRATULATIONS.
WELCOME TO ADULTHOOD.
I HAVE TO SAY "VICTORIOUS" IS
SUCH A HUGE HIT, EMMY NOMINATED.
YOU ARE ON THE COVER OF EVERY
MAGAZINE.
MILLIONS OF FANS.
DO YOU GET OVERWHELMED?
WHAT IS IT LIKE?
>> IT IS NOT NECESSARILY
OVERWHELMING.
IT IS EXCITING.
I HAVE THE SHOW AND THE
SOUNDTRACK RELEASED AND IT WAS
NUMBER FIVE ON THE BILLBOARD
CHARTS.
I'M SINGING A SONG ON THE
"FOOTLOOSE" SOUNDTRACK AND MY
FIRST ROLE IN A FEATURE FILM
COMING OUT NEXT OCTOBER.
>> YOU ARE BUSY.
>> YEAH.
>> YOU WENT TO A PERFORMING
ARTING HIGH SCHOOL AND YOUR SHOW
TAKES PLACE -- A PERFORMING ARTS
MIDDLE SCHOOL.
THE SHOW TAKES PLACE IN A
PERFORMS ARTING SCHOOL.
DID THAT PREPARE YOU?
>> DEFINITELY.
I HAD THREE HOURS OF SINGING,
ACTING AND DANCING LESSONS EVERY
DAY.
IT HELPED TRAIN MY VOICE.
I LEARNED A LOT.
MY LOVE FOR PERFORMING DEVELOPED
THERE.
>> YOU ARE ULTIMATELY PRETTY
BUSY AND SUCCESSFUL, BUT YOU
HAVE CARVED OUT TIME FOR OTHERS.
YOU ARE INVOLVED IN THE GIRL UP
CAMPAIGN AND YOU CAME BACK FROM
GUATEMALA.
TELL US ABOUT THAT.
>> IT WAS AMAZING.
I WAS AT THE VMA'S AND I FLEW TO
GUATEMALA, THE MESSAGE IS TO
BRING AWARENESS TO GIRLS IN THE
U.S. ABOUT GIRLS IN DEVELOPING
COUNTRIES THAT ARE SO BRIGHT AND
DESERVE AN EDUCATION AND DESERVE
OPPORTUNITIES AND DESERVE TO
HAVE A FUTURE LIKE ANYONE ELSE.
SO THAT IS WHAT WE ARE WORKING
ON.
IF YOU WOULD LIKE TO DOE NATE,
IT IS A GREAT ORGANIZATION.
>> SURE.
>> WHAT DO YOU HAVE IN YOUR
HAND?
>> I BROUGHT YOU AUTHENTIC
GUATEMALAN DOLLS.
THEY ARE VERY ANXIETY.
>> WORRY DOLLS.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>> WE ARE EXCITED.
CAN YOU TELL US ABOUT THE SONG
YOU ARE GOING TO BE SINGING?
>> YES.
I'M SINGING OFF THE "VICTORIOUS"
SOUNDTRACK.
IT IS CALLED "ALL I WANT IS
EVERYTHING."
IT IS PROBABLY MY FAVORITE SONG
TO PERFORM.
>> WE ARE LUCKY BECAUSE SHE IS
HERE TO PERFORM "ALL I WANT IS
EVERYTHING" OFF THE "VICTORIOUS"
SOUNDTRACK.
GIVE IT UP FOR VICTORIA JUSTICE.
&l I FEEL DELIRIOUS
COME LET'S GET OUT OF HE
WE'RE SO ANONYMOUS
BUT IT'S ALL COMING CLEAR
WE'RE HEADING FOR THE SKY
AND WE'LL GET LOST IN IT
CAUSE I WANT, ALL I WANT
ALL I WANT IS EVERYTHING &l
&l AND I WILL POSE IF I WANNA
I WILL VOGUE LIKE MADONNA
I MIGHT NOT DANCE LIKE MJ OR
R.I.P.
BUT I WILL GIVE THE BEST OF ME
ALL I WANT IS EVERYTHING
YES, EVERYTHING
TOO MUCH IS NOT ENOUGH FOR ME
BECAUSE I SICK OF SETTLING
FOR IN BETWEEN
AND I'M NOT GIVING UP
AS LONG AS IT FEELS RIGHT
AT LEAST WE KNOW THAT WE'RE
ALIVE
ALL I WANT IS EVERYTHING
YES, EVERYTHING, YEAH, OH
WE DON'T EVER STOP
LET'S WATCH THE SUN COME UP
WE'LL SLEEP WHEN WE'RE DEAD
HALFWAY KIND OF SUCKS
WE'RE HEADING FOR THE SKY
AND WE'LL GET LOST IN IT
BECAUSE ALL I WANT
ALL I WANT
ALL I WANT IS EVERYTHING
AND I WILL POSE IF I WANNA AND
I WILL VOGUE LIKE MADONNA
I MIGHT NOT DANCE LIKE MJ OR
R.I.P.
BUT I WILL GIVE THE BEST OF ME
A ALL I WANT IS EVERYTHING
YES, EVERYTHING
TOO MUCH IS NOT ENOUGH
I'M SICK OF SETLING FOR IN
BETWEEN
AND I'M NOT GIVING UP
AS LONG AS IT FEELS RIGHT
AT LEAST WE KNOW THAT WE'RE
ALIVE
ALL I WANT IS EVERYTHING
YES, EVERYTHING, YEAH, OH &l
&lOLD ON TO ME
AND I'LL HOLD ON TO YOU
DON'T OVERTHINK
WHAT HAVE WE GOT TO LOSE
IT'S ME AND YOU
ME AND YOU
NO MATTER WHAT
HOLD, HOLD
WE'RE HEADING FOR THE SKY
AND WE'LL GET LOST IN IT
BECAUSE ALL I WANT
ALL I WANT
ALL I WANT IS EVERYTHING
AND I WILL POSE IF I WANNA
AND I WILL VOGUE LIKE MADONNA
I MIGHT NOT DANCE LIKE M.J. OR
R.I.P.
BUT I WILL GIVE THE BEST OF ME
ALL I WANT IS EVERYTHING
YES, EVERYTHING
TOO MUCH IS NOT ENOUGH
I'M SICK OF SETLING FOR IN
BETWEEN
AND I'M NOT GIVING UP
AS LONG AS IT FEELS RIGHT
AT LEAST WE KNOW THAT WE'RE
ALIVE
ALL I WANT IS EVERYTHING
YES, EVERYTHING, YEAH, OH &l
>> I LIKE THAT SONG.
OUR THANKS TO VICTORIA JUSTICE.
YOU CAN CATCH A NEW EPISODE OF
"VICTORIOUS" THIS SATURDAY ON
NICKELODEON.
MEMBERS OF OUR AUDIENCE ARE
GOING HOME WITH THE SOUNDTRACK
ALBUM AND THE FIRST SEASON OF
THE SHOW ON DVD.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.